What's your favorite thing about Earth?
The Space Between Us is a romance, adventure, science
fiction film directed by Peter Chelsom.
A young man raised by scientists on Mars returns to Earth to find his father.
Gardner Elliot, played by Asa Butterfield.
Tulsa, played by Britt Robertson.
Kendra Wyndham, played by Carla Gugino.
Nathaniel Shepherd, played by Gary Oldman.
Sarah Elliot, played by Janet Montgomery.
Tom Chen, played by BD Wong.
The Space Between Us is a 2017 American romantic science fiction film directed by Peter Chelsom and
written by Allan Loeb, from a story by Stewart Schill, Richard Barton Lewis, and Loeb.
The film stars Gary Oldman, Asa Butterfield, Britt Robertson, and Carla Gugino,
and follows a teenage boy, born on Mars, who travels to Earth.
Principal photography began on September 14, 2015, in Albuquerque, New Mexico.
The film was released on February 3, 2017, by STXfilms.
It received negative reviews from critics and was a box office bomb,
grossing $16 million against its $30 million budget.
The film explores themes of future, planet mars, space
colony, fish out of water, scientist.
The tone is emotional and thought_provoking.